<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>AndreStork's Blog</title>
        <link>https://blog.andrestork.eu.org/</link>
        <description>A blog where Andre just writes random things about tech.</description>
        <item>
            <title>RCS now sucks</title>
            <link>http://blog.andrestork.eu.org/2023/06/rcs-now-sucks</link>
            <guid>rcs-now-sucks</guid>
            <updated>2023-06-06T14:30:00Z</updated>
            <description>Yes, the man who always loved RCS and found any reason to talk about it, finishes for hating it. Read the full article to know why.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>ONIMAI: it's not that bad as you might think</title>
            <link>http://blog.andrestork.eu.org/2023/03/onimai-is-not-as-bad-as-you-think</link>
            <guid>onimai-is-not-as-bad-as-you-think</guid>
            <updated>2023-03-31T14:30:00Z</updated>
            <description>I've lately began to get into CGDCT animes in the last weeks and the fault is mainly K-ON's. At the end I decided to begin with "ONIMAI: I'm Now Your Sister", based on the Nekotofu's manga of the same name, because a video that I saw inspired me to watch it. Read the full article to learn more about my watching pleasure.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>RCS deserves more attention</title>
            <link>http://blog.andrestork.eu.org/2022/12/rcs-deserves-more-attention</link>
            <guid>rcs-deserves-more-attention</guid>
            <updated>2022-12-19T20:30:00Z</updated>
            <description>In the last post I described how WhatsApp is bad and suggested to use RCS instead. And while it is true that RCS is really cool, it has many problems and a lot of them exist just because we don't consider it enough in the modern days of instant messaging apps.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>WhatsApp sucks. Why? And what should be done about it?</title>
            <link>http://blog.andrestork.eu.org/2022/11/whatsapp-sucks</link>
            <guid>whatsapp-sucks</guid>
            <updated>2022-11-11T14:30:00Z</updated>
            <description>So, if you live outside the U.S., there’s a very high chance that WhatsApp is the main messaging application that you and every other people use, but I have a bunch of things to say about it</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>ChromeOS: a review by a Windows (and occasional Linux) user</title>
            <link>http://blog.andrestork.eu.org/2022/09/chrome-os-review</link>
            <guid>chrome-os-review</guid>
            <updated>2022-09-29T14:15:00Z</updated>
            <description>For a couple of months now I've been using ChromeOS on my Huawei Matebook 14 and there are a lot of things I have to say.</description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
